(Leonard:)That sounds lovely.
(Sheldon:)It is if you
like bridge.
(Sheldon:)Do you like bridge,
Leonard?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I'm just not
dating someone right now.
(Leonard:)I don't need to go
to a senior center.
(Sheldon:)Meemaw resisted at first,
but now she loves it.
(Leonard:)Fine. If I don't meet someone
soon, you can put me in a home.
(Sheldon:)It's not a home.
It's a senior center.
(Sheldon:)We'd never put
Meemaw in a home!
(Leonard:)Hey, guys.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hey.
(Sheldon:)All right, I'll bow
to social pressure: Hey!
(Howard(phone rings):)Excuse me. That's my girlfriend,
Bernadette.
(Howard(phone rings):)I assigned her
her own ringtone--
"Bernadette,"
by The Four Tops.
(Howard(phone rings):)Hello, Bernadette.
(Raj:)When I call him, his phone
plays "Brown Eyed Girl."
(Raj:)Which, now that
(Raj:)I think about it,
is not so good.
(Leonard:)You realize he's just
rubbing our noses in the fact
(Leonard:)that he has a girlfriend,
and we don't.
You mean, you don't.
(Leonard:)You have a girlfriend?